sarraf.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy

**_Privacy Policy_**

* * *

Privacy Policy   
The Sarraf Jewelry privacy policy is your guarantee that any personal information you provide us will remain private. We ask for personal information so that we can provide you with a personal and customized shopping experience. Your personal information will never be sold to any third party for any reason. Sarraf Jewelry is committed to keeping your personal information private. Please review our privacy policy for more detail.

Privacy Commitment   
At Sarraf Jewelry, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We promise to keep all the information that you share with us confidential. We only collect personal information from customers in order to process billing, fulfill orders, and provide a personal and customized shopping experience. We do not share your information with any outside parties. 

How We Use The information We Gather  
When placing an order, you provide your name, mailing address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card number, and expiration date. For customers paying through alternative methods (such as a bank wire), additional information is required. We collect that information in order to: 

  * Verify your identity for payment authorization; 
  * Ship your order to you; 
  * Contact you regarding your order status; 
  * Personalize your shopping experience; 
  * Send you helpful information from Sarraf Jewelry; and, 
  * Generate anonymous statistics. 

Your personal information will be shared with your credit card company and the party through whom your product is shipped. This shared personal information includes all the following: 

  * your name; 
  * your e-mail address; 
  * your street address; 
  * your telephone number

Your personal information will not be sold to mailing-list firms or distributed to any of Sarraf Jewelry's partners without your permission. Although we may occasionally share statistics about our customers with important business partners, we do not disclose any identifying information about individual customers. If you elect to participate in a Sarraf Jewelry promotion (contest or sweepstakes), we will share your personal information with those organizations in order to ensure redemption of that promotion with the third-party partner managing that promotion. Further, Sarraf Jewelry provides you with access to third party partners to provide you certain services . If you decide to utilize these types of third party services , you will be directed to that third party's application. Sarraf Jewelry will provide that third party with your transaction information and then that third party will collect the additional information it needs in order to provide you with the requested service. Any information that you provide directly to that third party in connection with such services is covered by the privacy practices of such third party. Sarraf Jewelry is in no way responsible for the data collected or the privacy practices of any third party. You may want to consult the privacy policies of a third party prior to providing that third party with your address or other identifying information. 

Updating Personal Information  
If the personal information we've gathered from you changes or you no longer desire our service, we will gladly correct, update, or remove any personal data you have previously provided to us. To request a change or removal of your personal information, send e-mail to [sales@sarraf.com](mailto:sarraf@sarraf.com) or contact one of our customer service associates at 888-472-7723. 

**Secure Server**  
When you place an order with Sarraf Jewelry, you will be using our secure server. Our secure server software encrypts all of the personal information you submit to us. This helps to maintain the confidentiality of your information. 

**Cookies**  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer hard drive. You must have cookies enabled in order for you to be able to perform many of the general functions on the Sarraf Jewelry Web site. With cookies enabled, the Sarraf Jewelry Web site will have the capacity to deliver you a more customized and complete shopping experience, to track visits from our affiliates and partners, and to enable the use of our shopping cart. We do not use cookies to store or collect any personal information such as names, addresses, or payment information. If you remove our cookie from your hard drive, you will not be able to complete a search or a purchase on our site. To learn how to enable cookies on your computer, visit the Web site that corresponds to the browser you use: 

IP Address  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer and tune the operation of our site, and to log your browser type and referring URL information. Your IP address may also be used in collecting statistical data or in gathering broad usage information. Certain parts of this information may be shared with our partners, but your personal information will not be distributed. 

Changes in Privacy Policy  
If we modify this privacy policy, we will post a notice on our Web site. 

Opt Out of Receiving Communications  
To opt out of receiving communications from Sarraf Jewelry , you can make your request in person by contacting a customer service associate at 888-472-7723 or by e-mail at [sales@sarraf.com](mailto:sarraf@sarraf.com). 

Fraud Protection   
If a third party obtains your personal information from a purchase made with us and uses that information to perpetrate credit card fraud, you are protected. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank may hold you liable for $50 of fraudulent charges. If your bank holds you liable for any portion of the $50, Sarraf Jewelry Inc. will cover up to the entire $50.* 

Contacting Us   
If you have questions about this privacy statement, please contact our customer service department at [sales@sarraf.com](mailto:sarraf@sarraf.com) or at 888-472-7723. 

* Sarraf Jewelry will cover this liability if the unauthorized use resulted through no fault of yours from purchases made on Sarraf Jewelry's secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card company in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.

**Updated** **Jun 5, 2010**

**Questions?**  Contact [sales@sarraf.com](mailto:sarraf@sarraf.com) or 888-472-7723
